<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>M3rcuryLake</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on M3rcuryLake</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 00:55:26 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SSG and Ivory</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ssg-and-ivory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 00:55:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ssg-and-ivory/</guid>
      <description>Well&amp;hellip;As the Title suggests&amp;hellip;I have completed the static site generator which I was talking about in my previous post. Its up in my github account or follow this link to get there&amp;hellip;The motive behind this was pretty simple, I wanted a SSG which was customisable so that I can set it up with Tailwind css, not over-complicated but had all the things it was supposed to. For example, Hugo has some millions of parameters, shortcodes, partials and other things which baffled the heck out of me&amp;hellip;it took me nearly a week to understand how the hell to create a simple page with it, let alone setup tailwind css&amp;hellip;with postcss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lofi and life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/anupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 23:56:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/anupdate/</guid>
      <description>Sooo&amp;hellip;its been long since an update, and I felt kinda guilty for not being able to write anything (im lazy). Well, I pulled off some massive shits, like Lofi-Cafe, the heritage of this site, which functions by playing live streaming music from lofi girl&amp;rsquo;s channel on youtube and lets you listen to lofi without using that CPU intensive youtube site&amp;hellip;.and also saves your data&amp;hellip;which is pretty impressive. This thing was commited to this site last year early November or so&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lofi Cafe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/lofi-cafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:26:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/lofi-cafe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clouds Nowadays...</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/clouds-nowadays/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:21:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/clouds-nowadays/</guid>
      <description>Sooo&amp;hellip;.I have spend more than a hundred hours looking for a free vps, and I think I found it&amp;hellip;.a company by the name of mogenius.com allows users to create Ubuntu 18.04 VPS or Alpine Linux VPS (it also allows Nginx and other preconfigured templates and databses&amp;hellip;check out the docs for more info)&amp;hellip;guess what? I got one of those sweet Ubuntu bionic releases and it already feels good to know that I have spare PC in the cloud, to which I can ssh anytime I want&amp;hellip;They are like the &amp;ldquo;free alternative&amp;rdquo; to the high-end cloud services like digital ocean or linode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts?...</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 19:50:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Hiyaa, its my first time blogging and I am pretty lost for words, and content&amp;hellip;.both&amp;hellip;So lets just talk abt the new Onion server which i hosted&amp;hellip;previously, it was hosted on Heroku and yesterday night it was migrated to Render, who are gracious enough to keep a free plan without a credit card, but there are some downsides too.&#xA;Hosting a Onion server on heroku or render or any PaaS service is like fighting with a double eged sword&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
